{
    "subject": "resource/Boalkhali_Upazila",
    "predicate": "ontology/populationTotal",
    "object": "223125",
    "human_readable": "The population of Boalkhali Upazila is 223125.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9217379689216614,
            "question": "What is the population of Boalkhali Upazila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7406842112541199,
            "question": "Is the population of Boalkhali Upazila growing or shrinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7099408507347107,
            "question": "What are the implications of a large population for Boalkhali Upazila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7015195488929749,
            "question": "What factors might influence the population of Boalkhali Upazila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6961859464645386,
            "question": "What are some potential challenges facing the growing population of Boalkhali Upazila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6943451762199402,
            "question": "How many people live in Boalkhali Upazila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644931435585022,
            "question": "How might the future population of Boalkhali Upazila evolve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6405304074287415,
            "question": "What services and infrastructure are needed to support the population of Boalkhali Upazila?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6276280283927917,
            "question": "How does the population density of Boalkhali Upazila compare to other areas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.625718891620636,
            "question": "Compare the population of Boalkhali Upazila to other upazilas in Bangladesh."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The population of Boalkhali Upazila is 223125.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1813_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the population density of Boalkhali Upazila compare to other areas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1813_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services and infrastructure are needed to support the population of Boalkhali Upazila?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1813_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the future population of Boalkhali Upazila evolve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1813_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1813_59.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The population of Boalkhali Upazila is 223,125,\" as it is mentioned in one of the files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}